Dilshad iqbal

Instructor | Programmer

I'm studying MS (Computer Science) from Bahria University Lahore campus. I'm a game developer and Trainer. I have 2 years of experience in teaching (Home Tuitions) and 1.5 years plus experience in Unity 3d and 2d games. As a Professional Instructor and game developer, I want a highly rewarding career where I can use my skills and knowledge for organizational and personal growth.



dilshad2143@gmail.com

+923017036929

Lahore , Pakistan

February 15, 1994 🏥

linkedin.com/in/dilshad-iqbal43 in

dilshadiqbal2143 🔕

WORK EXPERIENCE

Game Developer

Let's Game

07/2018 - 09/2019

Lahore, Pakistan

TeachingHome Tutions

02/2016 - 03/2018

Faisalahad Pakistan

Trainer

Concepts Institute of Information Technology ♂

02/2018 – 04/2018

Faisalabad, Pakistan

Work as a Trainee in game development with C# programming.

Final Year Project (FYP)

University of Agriculture, Faisalabad

I completed my final year project on "Commando on Secret Mission" historical game for PC as like "Gta vise City". In this project, I took a part of the story (Commando series by A.Hameed) and made her game.

Game Developer

Loud Corp Games 🗷

04/2017 – 07/2017 Worked as an internee. Lahore, Pakistan

EDUCATION

MS(Computer Science)

Bahria University Lahore Campus 🗷

09/2019 – 09/2021

Lahore, Pakistan

BS (Computer Science)

University of Agriculture, Faisalabad

2014 – 2018 Faisalabad, Pakistan

Expertise

Courses

- Introduction to Computer
- Analysis of algorithms
- Operating system
- Software Engineering
- Computer architecture
- Object Oriented Programming
- Data Base Systems
- Data Structure
- Web programming
- Theory of automata

SKILLS

C# C++ OOP Artificial intelligence

Augmented Reality DBMS Operating System

Computer Architecture Data Structure HTML

CSS .NET Analysis of Algorithms MS Word

PowerPoint Excel Game Development

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Extreme Bike Racing:Impossible Stunts Game 2019

Highway Traffic Car Racer 🗹

FPS Animal Hunter: Free Deer Hunt 3D Games 🗹

Counter Terrorist Ops: Commando Mission 2019 🗹

Extreme GT Bike Stunts: Mega Ramp Racing Game 🛂

Impossible Car Racing 2019 🗹

Monster Truck Stunts 2019 🗹

Xtreme JetSki Racing: Overtake Challenge Games 🗹

Jet Ski Stunts: Water Boat Racing Game 🗹

RESEARCH AREA

1) A* Pathfinding algorithms in Augmented Reality (12/2019 – Present)

2) Max-Flow Network (09/2019 – 12/2019)

LANGUAGES

English Urdu
Professional Working Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Developing Critical Reading New ideas

Badminton Cricket News